const portInfoData = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "FTP",
      answer: "File Transfer Protocol",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "SSH",
      answer: "Secure Remote Access",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "SFTP",
      answer: "Secure File Transfer Protocol",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Telnet",
      answer: "Unsecure Remote Access",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "SMTP",
      answer: "Simple Mail Transfer Protocol",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "DNS",
      answer: "Domain Name Service",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "DHCP",
      answer: "Dynamic Host Control Protocol",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "TFTP",
      answer: "Trivial File Transfer",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "HTTP",
      answer: "Web Browsing",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "POP3",
      answer: "Receiving Emails",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "NTP",
      answer: "Network Time Protocol",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "NetBIOS",
      answer: "Windows File Sharing",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: "IMAP",
      answer: "Receiving Emails",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: "SNMP",
      answer: "Network Management",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: "LDAP",
      answer: "Directory Services",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: "HTTPS",
      answer: "Secure Web Browsing",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      question: "SMB",
      answer: "Windows File Sharing",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: "Syslog",
      answer: "System Logging",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: "SMTP TLS",
      answer: "Secure Sending Emails",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: "LDAPS",
      answer: "Secure Directory Services",
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: "IMAP SSL",
      answer: "Secure Receiving Emails",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: "POP3 SSL",
      answer: "Secure Receiving Emails",
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: "SQL",
      answer: "Database Communication",
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: "SQLnet",
      answer: "Oracle DB Communication",
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: "MySQL",
      answer: "MySQL DB Communication",
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: "RDP",
      answer: "Remote Desktop",
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: "SIP",
      answer: "VOIP and Video Calls",
    },
  ];
  
  export default portInfoData;
  